export default data = [
  {
      question: "Mastery of English _______ us with a very important tool for acquiring knowledge and information.",
      options: ["accesses","conveys","deprives","equips"],
      correct_option: "equips"
  },
  {
      question: "Languages change all the time. Many words that were found in Shakespeare’s works are no longer in _________ use.",
      options: ["absolute","current","repetitive","valuable"],
      correct_option: "current"
  },
  {
      question: "Do not just sit and wait _________ for a good chance to come to you. You have to take the initiative and create chances for yourself.",
      options: ["consciously","passively","reasonably","subjectively"],
      correct_option: "passively"
  },
  {
      question: "Identical twins have almost all of their genes in common, so any _______ between them is in large part due to the effects of the environment.",
      options: ["adoption","familiarity","stability","variation"],
      correct_option: "variation"
  },
  {
      question: "People believed in the _______ of the judge, so they were shocked to hear that he was involved in the bribery scandal.",
      options: ["inferiority","integrity","intimacy","ingenuity"],
      correct_option: "integrity"
  },
  {
      question: "The discovery of the new vaccine is an important _______ in the fight against avian flu.",
      options: ["breakthrough","commitment","demonstration","interpretation"],
      correct_option: "breakthrough"
  },
  {
      question: "To avoid being misled by news reports, we should learn to _______ between facts and opinions.",
      options: ["distinguish","complicate","reinforce","speculate"],
      correct_option: "distinguish"
  },
  {
      question: "After the big flood, the area was mostly ________, with only one or two homes still clinging to their last relics.",
      options: ["condensed","deserted","excluded","removed"],
      correct_option: "deserted"
  },
  {
      question: "In his speech, Dr. Huang presented all the reports about the energy crisis to _________ the need for developing new energy resources.",
      options: ["command","formulate","highlight","regulate"],
      correct_option: "highlight"
  },
  {
      question: "Hearing the art critic’s bitter and _______ comments on her new painting, Molly started a heated argument with him. ",
      options: ["outrageous","unreliable","urgent","glorious"],
      correct_option: "outrageous"
  },
]